Around the Circle Newsletter UP266
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Around the Circle Newsletter
2008 -- 2015
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts University Art Gallery
UP266
13 Digital Object(s)
116.31 Megabytes
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in one series, which is arranged chronologically.
Biographical / Historical
The Tufts University Art Gallery animates the intellectual life of the greater university community through exhibitions and programs exploring new, global perspectives on art and on art discourse. The Tufts University Art Gallery's exhibition space consists of the Tisch and Koppelman Galleries, the Remis Sculpture Court, a projection wall for short video and film works, and the Slater Concourse Gallery (Tufts' community gallery).
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the Around the Circle Newsletter, published by the Tufts University Art Gallery. In 2014, the title changed from Around the Circle to Tufts University Art Gallery.
- Around the Circle newsletter, 2008 -- 2015; UP266.001; 13 Digital Object(s); 116.31 Megabytes
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Around the Circle, Vol. 1, No. 1, 2008-08; UP266.000003; 1 Digital Object(s); 7.05 Megabytes
  - Around the Circle, Vol. 1, No. 2, 2009-01; UP266.000004; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.17 Megabytes
  - Around the Circle, Vol. 2, No. 1, 2009-08; UP266.000005; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.26 Megabytes
  - Around the Circle, Vol. 2, No. 2, 2010-02; UP266.000006; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.9 Megabytes
  - Around the Circle, Vol. 3, No. 1, 2010-08; UP266.000007; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.4 Megabytes
  - Around the Circle, Vol. 3, No. 2, 2011-01; UP266.000008; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.33 Megabytes
  - Around the Circle, Vol. 4, No. 1, 2011-08; UP266.000009; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.19 Megabytes
  - Around the Circle, Vol.4, No. 2, 2012-01; UP266.000010; 1 Digital Object(s); 4.64 Megabytes
  - Around the Circle, Vol. 5, No. 1, 2012-09; UP266.000011; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.16 Megabytes
  - Around the Circle, Vol. 5, No. 2, 2013-01; UP266.000012; 1 Digital Object(s); 5.97 Megabytes
  - Tufts University Art Gallery, Spring 2014; UP266.000014; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.44 Megabytes
  - Tufts University Art Gallery, Fall 2014; UP266.000013; 1 Digital Object(s); 36.1 Megabytes
  - Tufts University Art Gallery, Spring 2015; UP266.000015; 1 Digital Object(s); 30.7 Megabytes